Hey guys, welcome back to the channel
and welcome to a new video. I am
standing here in my new and improved
workroom craft room area. So, if you
caught my latest video, it was the big
reveal of my craft room workroom no
spend challenge. So, I made over this
whole area after our house fire using
only things that I already had in my
home. I didn't buy anything. I didn't go
out and get anything to improve the
space. I just worked with what I already
have. So, I am super excited to be doing
my very first video here in my new
workroom studio. Well, new to me.
So, anyways, if you haven't caught that
video, I hope you'll go back and check
it out. But today I wanted to unbox some
craft supplies from Teimu. Now Timu,
Teimu, however you say it. I'm gonna say
Teimu because that's what I've always
called it. But anyways, so as you know,
or maybe you don't know if you're new to
my channel for the first time, we had a
house fire back in November of 2024. We
are still trying to put our house back
together. It has been a long, tiring,
gruesome journey and we are just getting
started at putting everything back
together.
But the bad news about the fire was I
lost pretty much my whole craft room.
That's right. Over 11 years of crafting
and gathering supplies and getting
materials, tools, you name it, gone. My
craft room was directly beside where the
fire was. So, pretty much everything in
that room got pitched. So, I am starting
over from scratch. And I thought I would
take this opportunity to buy a few
things from Teimu to see how great their
stuff really is, if it's worth it, if
it's not. So, I want to unbox it here
together on my YouTube channel, a real
live review of craft supplies or
materials that you can craft with from
Teimu to see what they're legitly like.
So, I hope you enjoy this video. Please
leave me a comment below. Let me know
what you think throughout the whole
video. I love reading your guys's
comments. So, please, please, please
comment. It means the world to me. And
we're going to go ahead and get to this
big package.
So, this is my package here.
I got a lot of stuff, you guys. I got a
whole craft room I got to replenish. So,
it's going to take me some time. But,
and to be honest, I ordered so much I
can't really remember. So, it's like
Christmas all over again, and I'm going
to be able to see and open up and be
surprised, just as surprised as you guys
are. So, let's get into this package.
Okay, so the first thing out of the bag
is not a craft supply.
I'm off to a great start, you guys. This
is actually a scarf. To be fair, a lot
of my scarves got thrown out and it was
there and it was a great price. Um, I'm
going to as I'm not gonna I cannot
remember the prices of all the things.
So, as I'm talking, I'm going to put up
a little graphic of what everything the
price actually was because for me to
remember, it's just too much. But so
far, this scarf isn't actually too bad.
Um, I would say it's maybe comparable to
something that you would get at like the
dollar store, Dollarama. Now, remind
you, I'll remind you guys, all this
stuff is coming from China and it is on
Teimu, so the quality of some things may
not be the greatest. Um, but I would
totally wear this and I don't think if I
wore it, people would be people would
think it was from there. So,
I think uh this one this one gets a
pass. Um maybe actually for fun, I'll
give things a rating out of 10. So, I'm
going to give this a six out of 10. I'll
give this scarf a six out of 10. Next
up, we have a box here. I don't know
what's in this box. I have no idea. I
cannot even remember half the stuff I
ordered.
Let's open it up.
Another
box inside of a box. Oh, two boxes. See?
Oh, the candles. Okay, I remember this.
So, these are supposed to be flickering
flameless candles.
They take
batteries, unfortunately. H, you know
what? That's the kind of thing that's
really annoying about these. These are
going to take a lot of batteries, you
guys.
Twist open the battery cover. Twist it
off. I don't know how many batteries
it's going to each one is going to take.
Maybe three or two looks like a
batteries. So, this was a 12-pack that I
got
and I bought them for upstairs in my
candlesticks because I have real candles
up there, but it makes me very nervous.
I'm going to go test these out so that
we can give the proper ranking and
proper score. So, I'm going to go get
some batteries in these. Okay, you guys.
So, each candle takes two batteries,
which isn't too bad, I suppose, but the
only way to turn them on or off is to
loosen this.
So, I'm just showing I had to put my
phone on the tripod here. But look, you
have to either
unloosen, loosen. There's no remote.
There's no onoff switch. So, let's put
them in a candle holder and let's see.
Okay, I will give it to them. It looks
pretty cool in the candle holder. Um, it
doesn't look overly fake fake. And I
love how they're an off-white. Um, I'm
going to set the rest up. Hopefully, I
have enough batteries. And let's see.
All right, guys. I only had enough
batteries to do the first six candles.
And I am so sad about this because they
are actually really nice.
And after a while, if you notice, the
flames start to flicker.
Do you see it there?
I don't know if the camera picks it up,
but they are flickering. Like they're
they're they're slowly flating and
flickering, but there's no way to turn
them on or off without taking the
candles right out of the candlestick and
unscrewing the base just a little bit.
So, in order for me to put these on, I
would have to go into every single
candlestick and turn the thing. And I
just don't think that's very um I don't
think that's very uh what's the word?
Effective, time effective. You know, if
they had a little remote, it would be so
much better. So, for these,
unfortunately,
I was going to give them like a two. I'm
gonna give them a four because they are
really cool when they're on and they
look really nice. Not cheap looking at
all, but because there's no remote,
there's no H. That's really sad,
but I'll give them a four out of 10.
Okay, guys. I don't want to do this um
in editing. I want to figure it out
right now. I want to figure out how much
these candles cost because I am really
sad about that. that had the potential
to be a really great product.
Um, oh, here they are.
Worth $31.
I paid $31 for those.
Dang.
See a lot of comments saying people
saying that you're they're using them
for a wedding. So, I guess if you're
using them for a wedding, you just go
around and flick them all on.
But like
I would
that makes me really sad.
They should have had a remote with it.
If they had a remote that would be so
much better. Oh my word. Then this is
where I get really annoyed because
there's a set.
But these ones don't look as nice.
They're $16 and they come with a remote.
Darn.
Okay. Well, moving on. All right. Next
up, we've got some ribbon. This ribbon
is actually really nice. This is
actually really nice ribbon. And I'm
actually going to open up and take the
plastic off. Uh the color though, I wish
it was more red. It's more of a
burgundy. Actually, it's not bad though.
But that's really nice ribbon. I'll give
you a closeup. It's not cheap um that
cheap shiny stuff. It's actually velvet.
And the gold is actually really, really
nice.
So, I am going to give this ribbon. And
actually, you know what? I said I was
going to flash the prices up later, but
I can't give an accurate rating if I
don't know the price. Okay, so let me
just go back to my orders here. This
ribbon was $457.
So, I am going to give this and it looks
like quite a bit. It's not stingy
either.
Um, I'm I'm going to give this an eight
out of 10. That's good. I'm I'm I'm
happy with that. Next up, we have some
stickers. This was a sticker pack.
We've got
the these look very AI made. Um, but
they're very cute.
Warm holiday glow.
I do love this one. Look at how cute
this one is. That one is really cute.
And I feel like I could use these to
make little Christmas signs.
Um, this one's really nice, too. And so
far, there's no spelling mistakes
cuz sometimes with this you get things
spelled weird. Santa's bakery. Yeah,
these are really cute. Um, holiday cheer
inside. Oh, you could put that on a
little present. That's so cute. Um, I
just want to see them all before I move
on here. All right, let's see how much
these were. These stickers were $3.87.
I am going to give them a
seven out of 10. No, I'm going to give
them an eight. I'm going to give them an
eight out of 10. I think they'll be
great for crafting. There's no spelling
mistakes and they do look very cute. So,
we'll give those an eight out of 10. All
right.
I'm laughing, you guys, because I
actually ordered this twice. I ordered
it accidentally twice. So, I have
another one of these coming. And on the
site, it looks so cool. It looks like
it's a tin old tin sign.
It's just, you know, cheap bass wood,
balsa wood, whatever that cheap crafting
wood is called. It looks a little faded.
Um, it's meant to look old. Came with
these little stickers to hang it up
somewhere. You could use it in the
middle of a wreath. I think it would
look really cute. baby. I paid $347
for this. Uh, I think it's all right. I
mean, I think you could find something
similar at the dollar store at Dollar
Tree for $1.25.
So, I think the pricing is a little bit
off. And they're kind of presenting it
as something bigger and better. So, I'm
going to give this a four. No, I'm going
to give it a three. Sorry, you get a
three out of 10. But, you know what? I
will probably use it for crafting. I'll
work it into something like an
arrangement or something.
There we got some more ribbon.
Hey, look at this everybody.
They use my little say my little
straight pin trick. If you caught that
in the other video, my video that I just
posted about my um big reveal for my
workroom for the ribbon, the straight
pin trick. This is actually a trick that
my mother taught me. She worked at a uh
not work, she owned a floral shop and uh
she had all her ribbons on her ribbon
rack and she had straight pins on all of
them so they don't unwind and hang down
and droop. Um so yeah, kudos to my
mother for that little tip and they know
it too. So this is some um ribbon. It
looks like jute ribbon I bought in a
little pack. Great for crafting. The
quality is great. Not bad. Uh, I paid
$522
for this. They make it look a little
better in the picture. Um,
but they're not bad. They're really
nice. I'm going to give this a 7 out of
10. Nice crafting ribbon. The price is
good for that. Okay. And then I got
these little papers. I love for
Christmas crafting having lots of nice
papers do with like backgrounds and
stuff. So, this is some like music note
paper here with some holly on it. The
quality is not overly the greatest. This
one's a little weird. That looks like
blood splatter
on the music notes. Not really fond of
that one, but I think Are these
stickers? They are. They're adhesive.
So, these are stickers. So, that's kind
of great. I could use them on like the
backing of signs or something like to
make a sign. I'm not sure what all this
is about. Like I think it's trying to
make it look rustic, but to me it just
looks like blood.
Um, let's see how much we paid for
those. $411.
And they are sticky. And the pictures on
the site are pretty bang on to what I
actually got. So, I'll give this a 6 out
of 10.
The one thing I do really love, and I've
ordered these before, is their little
rustic pieces for crafting with, um, I
think they do a really good job of
these, except for now I got, like, look
at how rusty and unique and different
these are, and they look legit. So, this
is a pack of rustic stars. I'm just
going to put some in my hand so you guys
can see. I really do like their rustic
little elements. I have bought these
before, so I knew that going into this.
This was a 50 pack for $7.64.
Um, I think that's a great price. Um,
Michaelels would probably be a lot more.
I'm gonna give this a 10 out of 10. Very
happy with this. I've ordered them
before. I love those.
Okay, next up, we have some washi tape.
So, this is a package of washi tape
here. To be honest, I expected these to
be a little bit bigger, but that's okay.
And by bigger, I mean like wider, but I
guess washi tape is kind of small. But
like look at this little one. I mean I
guess different lengths are good for
different things. These ones are really
small you guys.
But these ones here, like look at the
little gingerbread men.
They are so cute. And until I use these
and see how they actually stick and
everything, I can't really give a fair
rating. Um but there's a lot of variety
in here. Great for Christmas crafting.
Pretty happy with this. I suppose the
washi tape was $9.94.
Oo, paid a bit more for that than I
thought.
But I mean, in compare comparison to
like you're shopping at Michaels or
something, I I'll give it a uh I'll give
it a seven out of 10. That's a lot of
washi tape. Next up, some more ribbon.
Oh, I got two things here. Some ribbon.
This is just ribbon for crafting. It's
nice. Quite a bit.
Let's see what the price is. $2.86.
That's pretty good. And it's generic
gingham red ribbon for crafting for
Christmas. That gets a 9 out of 10.
Oh, the second thing I picked out of
that looks like some little stickers.
They get me with the stickers, you guys.
They really do. These are clear
stickers. Thought maybe they'd be nice
for crafting somewhere. Oh, look at this
little lady. This little vintage lady.
She's so small.
Oh, and the little kitties in the
stocking.
I honestly I'm not going to show you all
of them, but these were vintage and I
thought they were cute. I don't know how
they're going to look when I put them on
things, but I really am into the vintage
Christmas. I really love it. Look at
this little reindeer in the sweater. And
he's got all his hoops. He's got all
four hoops. Sometimes with this stuff,
you never know what you're going to get.
Oh, look at the little bunny with the
Christmas tree. Okay, these are pretty
cute. I'll give them that. Those are
pretty cute. Let's see how much we paid
for them. So, this was a 50 pack of
vintage Christmas mousse stickers. They
call them DIY waterproof. $2.87.
That gets a nine out of 10.
[Music]
All right. Now, this I've actually
bought these little banners before, and
I have a real on my Instagram page where
I jujued up one of these and made it a
little bit better.
It's linked in the description.
So, I bought another one.
Oh,
you guys. This one is so bad.
Look at their faces.
It's not You can tell it's like AI
redone vintage. I mean, but from a
distance, like I think from a distance
it'll be okay. But like this one, like
he doesn't even have any eyeballs.
They're not really there.
But it's still cute, I suppose. It's
just some of the images are very weird,
you know,
like this one. They don't they don't
really have faces, you know? But I think
these are really cute to work into
banners, maybe a wreath. Not overly
happy with the quality of the photos on
this one, but it is vintage. So, like,
it's supposed to be vintage. Okay, this
one's a little creepy.
I'm sorry. This one is going to get a
five. No, a four. This one's going to
get a four. The pictures could have been
better.
I've had other I've bought other ones
where the pictures are really nice, so I
know they can be better. So, that one
gets a four.
Oh, I didn't tell you how much it was.
It was $5.92.
So, yeah. Still gets a what did I say? A
four, I think. All right. Here's another
little garland. This one is looking a
little better. More AI generated images,
though. But at least their faces are
clear.
This one is cute. I This one is very
cute. Oh, look at the little girl with
the music notes. Good cheer. I do like
this one.
Oh, I love this. I love this one. I I
tell you guys, I love the vintage
Christmas. I am so doing vintage
Christmas this year. I just need
the old, you know? I just need to Oh, I
love this one, too. This one is really
cute. This one gets a nine out of 10.
No, this one gets a 10 out of 10. I I'm
loving this one. Look at the little
bird.
So cute. They give you these. I don't
know what those are for, but Oh, maybe
for the They're postcards. That's what
they are. So, to seal the envelope,
maybe. So, that one's not a banner.
They're actually postcards, but I feel
like you could turn it into a banner.
This item is sold out.
What? But it won't tell me what it was,
how much it was, cuz it was sold out.
Doesn't even tell me in my order.
I'm going to guess it was around the
same price as the other one. See? Or Oh,
here it is. $41. Yeah, that's good for
that. All right. And then this is what I
was really drawn to on their site is all
these little bits and bobs of greenery
cuz these are great for crafting, you
guys. So, like look at these. They're
the perfect size to just stick into
things like and you put a little bell
there like to work in the little bits of
greenery when you're um crafting and
doing stuff. These are amazing and the
quality is really good. I was super
excited to get these rather than buying
big picks and pulling things off. So,
this is really nice. I'm really happy
with this. $4.81.
No, I got a Did I get a 50 pack? Well,
the 25 pack is $4.80.
The 50 pack is $7.58.
And I don't know if there's 25 or 50 in
here. I don't know which pack I got. Oh,
no. It says 50 right there. So, I got
the 50 pack. That I'm really happy with
those. 10 out of 10.
[Applause]
Oh, and apparently I bought more.
So, this is the
say on this one. This one must have been
a different seller
and they are a little bit different.
These ones are really nice, too. So,
happy with that. Again, I like these are
just so handy to have for Christmas
crafting.
Highly, highly recommend that.
Those ones may be a little bit better
than the last ones. They're a little
more realistic looking. Oh, here they
are. Another 50 piece from a different
seller. $5.91.
Pretty good.
Okay. More
scrapbooking paper or whatever you want
to call this. Or maybe these are
stickers.
All right. Let's see how these look.
These ones aren't stickers. These are
actually scrapbooking paper.
They're really nice. They're not bad.
Oh, this one's cute. They're very thin.
Like, they're very thin. They're not
card stock. They're paper, but they
would be nice for crafting.
I like that little girl. She's sweet.
That one's a little weird.
Oh, this one doesn't have a face.
That's okay. This one looks like Judy
Garland a little bit. And then we got
vintage. And then we have this like
modern lady with a modern toque on. So
that's a little weird. This one's cute
though.
Cute. Very cute. Yeah. So there's a lot
of these. Oh, I do like this one with
the church though. Where did it go? Oh,
this one's nice, too, with the big
Christmas tree. Little carolers.
This one with the church. That's very
vintage looking. Very nice. Yeah, these
are nice. Okay, let's see how much these
were.
24 6x6 inch.
It says they're stickers, but they're
not.
So, that's a lie.
Snow scene stickers. It says they're
stickers. They're not.
Anyways, they were $4.32.
So, they're kind of nice. I'm going to
give this one a six just because they
said they're stickers and they're not.
So, that's kind of false. So, if you
bought these planning on them being
stickers, you'd be severely
disappointed. Um, but they're they're
okay. We'll give them a six. Nice little
crafting supplies. Then we've got a big
box. Oh, these are more candles. Did I
order more candles? Oh, these are the
pillar candles. Well, they're really
skinny.
But at least these ones come with not
one remote, but two remotes.
Hey, maybe this remote will work for the
other thing. Why do I got two remotes?
Wouldn't that be great if it worked for
the other candles?
Um,
these take
two AA batteries,
which I'm out of AA batteries, but I'm
going to have to go and take them out of
the candles upstairs
to test these out
so that I can give my full and honest
review. So, let's go do that. All right,
guys. So, these ones have two covers
inside.
So, we're going to pop some batteries in
here. If I can see which way they go.
Try that.
Okay.
So, we've got that. And then we've got
this cover that goes back in here.
And there's a little offon switch
underneath the candle, too. So, I've
turned it on. And then you've got this
cover that goes back on.
That was really hard to get on.
I don't think that's on right.
Really hard to get on.
It doesn't line up right.
Come on. Okay. Anyways,
so there's that. Now, let's see the
remote.
It's flickering. It's flickering.
Okay. Remote works.
2 hour, 6 hour, 4 hour, 8 hour, light
candle,
and then there's dim settings. So, you
can turn it down or you can turn it up.
Hey, these are pretty cool. Not bad.
And I've got three different sizes.
I wish they were a little fatter, but um
set them up and see.
The one annoying thing about these is
this bottom piece. Like, it's so tight
and hard to get off and then to get back
on. And I'm afraid the candles aren't
going to sit flat if I don't get it
perfectly lined up.
I don't know why you need that, but
safety feature, I guess. Maybe to
protect the batteries.
Oh, these bottoms. Ow.
Like,
I can't even get this one off.
There. That one went off easy.
Weird.
Guys, I'm going to forget the bottoms. I
don't care. They're annoying.
Don't care.
All right, guys. So, they do look pretty
nice. I will give them that. And I do
like that they didn't I could take the
bottom off cuz I have this little brush
dish that is made for a real candle.
It's got that pointy thing and I can
just put it over top and it stays. So
that was nice. Um I like that there's a
remote. So that's a oneup on the other
candles. So I can turn them off and on.
I can set them for a timer. I can dim
them, make them brighter. They're pretty
nice. I'll give them that.
The only thing is though, when I turn
these on, this remote also controls the
candles
from another set that I bought at T-Mu.
So, I was like, when I turned these on
and I was messing around, I was like,
"How long have those candles been on?
who turned those on and then I realized
this remote was controlling all of them.
So, watch. Let's see if I can get a
shot.
Don't mind the mess. I had my couches
delivered and they weren't right. So,
they got to go back. Let's see. Off.
Yeah.
So, now I can control all the candles.
If only I could control those candles.
So, the pillar candles. Let's find them
here and see the price.
So, it's a 12-pack flameless LED candles
with remote timer.
Uh $25.49. So, they're less than the
taper candles, and they come with a
remote.
I'm pretty impressed. I'll admit it. I
like I said, I wish they were a little
bit wider, but I'm going to give these a
seven out of 10. And they could be a
little bit more realistic looking.
They're a little fake, but yeah, we'll
give them a seven out of 10. Next up, I
bought some wrapping paper. I love
wrapping paper for crafting. It got a
little damaged in shipping. Nutcracker
pink um wrapping paper. I can use it for
wrapping, but you can also use it for
crafting. It's pretty nice. The faces
are all nice. Sometimes you got to worry
with this stuff if it's AI generated.
The faces look weird. This is actually
pretty nice wrapping paper. And it looks
like there's quite a bit of it. So,
let's see. It's not your typical size
though in um in length. Like it's a lot
shorter than regular wrapping paper.
Oh my goodness.
I paid $1055
for this.
Why did I do that?
What was I thinking? $10
almost $11 for this. I fig I must have
had some kind of a craft in mind. I must
have I don't know. It must have been
impulse buy. I don't know. That was very
weird. I don't I wouldn't say this is
worth $10,
man. I'm disappointed in myself. Very
disappointed.
Maybe I used a coupon or something.
Anyways,
because of the price, I'm going to give
this a four out of 10. I do not think it
is worth $10, but all right, we got some
more ribbon. Again, sealed with the
straight pins. Love it. Love it. Love
it. Love it that they they pin these
with the straight pins rather than
taping them. Very nice crochet lace
style ribbon. This is great for
crafting, especially at Christmas and
fall time. Can never have too much of
this stuff.
And I bought a variety pack with
different styles and thicknesses. So,
there's these two thicker ones. The
thinner ones I'm just going to show you
guys. Very, very nice ribbon. Very, very
nice.
Wish it was on a spool, but that's okay.
So, the crochet ribbon was $1521
and there is 25 yards total. So, 5 yards
in each, which is pretty good. If you
had to go into a craft store and buy
this stuff, it would be a lot more than
that. So,
and the quality is good. So, I'm going
to give that a 9 out of 10.
No, I'm going to give that a 10 out of
10. No, I'm going to give it a 9 out of
10 because I wish it was on a spool.
There. Done. Okay, look at this.
So, this caught my eye. These are pages.
Like, they look like they're from a
book. So, we've got some that look like
they're from a newspaper. I always
wonder what these things actually say.
If they're actually taken from an old
newspaper. This says Friday, December
the 18th, 1863. That's good for
Christmas crafting. This is the bacon
for breakfast.
Anyways, okay. And then these look like
they're from a dictionary. Some map
paper. This looks like an old ledger.
Very nice looking. Very legit looking.
And it's they're not very blurry. Like
they're not they're not blurry. They're
very crisp and very clear. This looks
like it's from like an old math
textbook. And then my favorite little
music notes, gardening little gardening
pages with all kinds of botanicals. So,
these are just this is just for like not
specifically for Christmas crafting per
se, but I just love having different
types of papers. And let's see how much
this was. 240 pieces of vintage
scrapbooking paper, newspaper, magazine,
botanical for $2153.
I think that is a good price for
scrapbooking paper cuz scrapbooking
paper is really expensive. They're not a
big size by any means, but I think
they're perfect for crafting. I'm going
to give this an eight out of 10.
Here we have some more stickers. The
stickers on team really get me, you
guys. I just I don't know why. I just
love them. Ah,
not going to lie, a little disappointed
with these ones.
Look at how small they are. They're so
tiny. Like, look at this little beep.
Like, it's so tiny. Look at this one.
Like I suppose if you were scrapbooking,
these would be perfect. I don't
scrapbook. I craft. But maybe they'll be
good for like a little thing. Like this
could this could make like a cute super
cute little banner if I was doing
something like a little miniature or
something. Like I know I will put these
to use. I'm just a little disappointed
with the size. Oh, and here's my
favorite.
Has to be Holly Jolly cuz that's my
name. Yeah. Christmas stickers, cartoon
themed, self adhesive, 100 pieces,
$6. Okay, this is like this is the
picture, you guys. I don't know if you
can see that. I'm I'm going to put the
actual picture on here rather than show
you. I'll flash it up here. They look
really big, you know, like they look
bigger than what they actually are. So,
I'm a little disappointed in the size,
but they're still cute. But because of
the size, I'm going to give that a five
out of 10.
[Music]
And more paper. Apparently, I was in a
paper mood, you guys. But like I said, I
lost all my craft supplies. I lost all
of them. These ones are cute. These ones
are super cute. Little vintage
wallpapers.
Oh, these are cute. Yeah. Come on.
Super super cute. Really happy with
these. I love this one. This little
winter scene. So nice.
Maybe I'm going to become a scrapbooker.
scrapbooker, you guys. Okay, let's see
here. Let's see. Okay, so that was this
one. 24 sheets of Christmas scrapbooking
paper, uh 6x6. So, when you're shopping
on Teimu, you really got to pay
attention to the sizes because when they
show you the picture, this looks like
one of those big packs like you would
get at Michaels, you know, but it's not.
They're 6x6, so you always got to check
the size. But this was only $5.26. I'm
pretty happy with that. I'm going to
give that a
eight out of 10.
All right. Now, we've got these. What is
this? What did I buy? Vintage time and
paper tape. What did I think I was going
to do with this? I don't scrapbook. Why
did I buy all this stuff? It is nice
though.
Like, I think I was just thinking I
really want to get it. My mom makes
primitives and I really want to start
doing more primitive rustic stuff. So,
maybe that's what I was thinking here.
So, it's like a tape, right? A thick
tape. Um, a wide tape that you can use
on I really like this one with the old
post stuff. So, let's see what I did
with that. What's the price there? So,
the rolls of inched tape. Well, they
call it washi tape online. 735 for this.
Yeah, I suppose that's all right. Four
rolls vintage. Uh, seven out of 10. Only
because I don't know why I bought that.
No, I'm just kidding. It's pretty good.
We'll give it an eight out of 10. Okay.
And then these I bought before too last
year. And again, like I said with the
rustic stars, I love these. These are
little rustic Christmas trees that you
can hang on things and use for all your
primitive rustic Christmas crafting.
Love them. This is a 10 piece pack. 10
pieces for $4.15.
Those are a little more, but I craft
with these and I use them and I love
them. That's a 10 out of 10.
Okay. What is this? Okay. I feel like
this is going to be a disappointment
greatly. What is this
wrinkly old velvet ribbon? I hope I did
not pay more than a dollar for this.
That's got to be a mistake. Please be a
mistake. No. Come on. I paid $253
for that.
Come on. like
one piece of velvet ribbon.
I guess I can make one bow.
What? And you know what's annoying? I'll
show the picture, you guys. They have it
presented like it's a nice roll. Like,
come on. I mean, I guess it does say one
and a half yards, but like you're
telling me that's that's that's the
length of a yard stick. This is not one
and a half yards.
Anyways, boo on that. That gets a one
out of 10. And I give that a zero out of
10.
More stickers. But they're cute. I'll
give them that. They're cute. The nice
books with the bells. And I figure I'm
going to be using these for some sort of
Christmas crafting.
This one's cute. You never know. Okay,
the stickers. Like I said, the stickers
get me. But let's see how much they
were. I feel like I've missed something
here in my something in my order is
missing. Yes.
Or maybe it's over there.
Oh, yeah. There were two there were two
things I took out of the bag beforehand.
They're not missing. They're over there.
Sorry. Let me get to these stickers. I'm
getting off track here. $155 for 50
stickers. That's good. I'll give that a
nine out of 10. Okay, let me find Let me
get this thing because I took it out
beforehand. So, this is supposed to be a
tree. I'm going to flash up the picture
of what I thought.
No way.
No way. No. This is not a tree. This is
a bushel. Like,
this is supposed to be a tree. Okay.
This is supposed to be that tree. It has
to be. There's a there's supposed to be
a lighted garland that I haven't seen.
Oh, it does say without basin.
No way. Okay, this is not. And then the
comments are like, "Love it. It's great
for my winter pots and it looks quite
real." Oh, somebody did comment. Not
what the picture shows. No, absolutely
not. Look at this picture that somebody
posted or they posted. Get real. Get
real right now. Okay, look at this. I
got to pull the camera up. See if we can
make any any sense of this at all. So,
this is the tree, you guys. This tree is
this tree.
Don't think so. And no. Okay. So, if we
pull if we start at the bottom and we
pull the branches down, maybe I'll be
pleasantly surprised. Let's keep an open
mind here.
Okay. What in the world?
Like, it it's not even going to go that
way because there's nothing on this
side. It's flat.
Or do you have to work it yourself? Like
what in the world? These ones don't even
bend. Oh, there we go.
Let's not be negative right off the
start. Holy. Let's just give it a try.
Okay, you guys. Like Charlie Brown's
Christmas tree looks better than this.
Let me try to fluff this out.
Okay. Is that the top? Is that the top?
Is that the top? I don't know.
Okay.
Okay,
here's our tree, guys.
What do you guys think?
Okay, like disappointed.
Disappointed.
I'm going to see how much I paid for
this and then that'll be the deciding
factor if I send it back cuz sending it
back would be a lot of work, I think.
But like
I could use the branches for other
things. Like I could take it apart and
use the branches for other things. Like
I will not let it go to waste. Trust me
on that. But maybe if I put it in a pot,
maybe we can make something out of it.
Maybe I shouldn't be so negative. Maybe
we can make like our own little Charlie
Brown Christmas tree looking thing.
Maybe I could put some of the vintage
stuff with it. Like And the But the
pieces are already starting to fall out.
Okay, let's see. Let's see how much we
paid for this. I paid $15 for this. So,
am I okay? They say it's regularly $43.
If I paid $43 for this, somebody would
be getting something. Okay.
They say it's 23.62 in. I'll be the
judge of that.
Let's see here. Okay. It's 23.62 62 in.
We'll calm down. Okay. They've sold 664
of these. No doubt. Because this is what
the picture looks like.
Does that look like that?
It's so full.
And not to mention the the stem in the
middle looks so realistic.
I I'm going to think on that if I'm
going to bother with the return. I'm
probably not because it was only $15 and
I will use the greenery. If I don't
think of something else to make with it
first or to even try to actually make it
look good, I am definitely giving that a
one. That gets a one out of 10. 100% a
one. That is not what it says at all.
Okay.
Now, my lighted garland. So, before I
open this, I'm going to show you guys
the picture. All right, I'm going to put
the picture up here. This lighted
garland is 6 feet realistic pre-lit
Norfolk pine. $14.96.
So, we only paid $14 for it. So, keep
that in mind, folks. It is very plastic.
Like very plastic. Does not smell nice.
Very, very plastic. It's six feet, but
it's not very full.
And not only is it not very full,
they give you the lights in a little
bag. You got to put them on yourself.
So, it is not pre-lit because the lights
come in a bag.
Like, that is not pre-lit. I'm going to
have to work these around there. I'm
trying not to be negative, but that's
really annoying. Like, and I get it's
only $14, but it's not pre-lit because
the lights are not on it. You know how
hard it is to hide lights and things.
Yeah. Disappointed in this one as well.
This one gets a two.
Um, it is not realistic. It is plastic.
I would not recommend that garland. I
mean, maybe if you want a garland for a
good price, like if you want just a
garland, like for a price, it's
certainly better than anything you'd see
in the dollar store. Actually, no,
that's not true because I've seen some
really nice garlands in the dollar
store. So, that's not even true. Um, but
yeah, it gets a two. It gets a two. It
did come with the lights, I suppose. So,
it gets a pass there.
But anyways, you guys, that's my haul.
Let me know what you think. What are
your thoughts on these Teemo Teu, sorry,
products? Let me know. Put it in the
comments below. If you would like to see
more videos like this, I would love to
share them with you. Let me know your
thoughts and um if it shakes it up a
little bit between the crafting and if
you like this style of content, let me
know. I love ordering stuff and testing
it out before I post about it. I don't
like just posting about things that I
haven't seen or touched or felt or used
myself because I like to keep things
really honest here with you guys. So,
let me know in the comments. Thank you
so much for tuning into this video. I am
going to get crafting right now. I've
already started building up my craft
tools and my craft supplies and it is
time to do a little fall crafting today.
So, I'm going to move right on from this
and start my fall crafting and there'll
be a video coming real soon on a fall
Dollar Tree crafting roundup. So, stay
tuned for that. Hit the like and
subscribe if you want to see more
content from me. And until next time,
we'll see you later, guys.
[Music]
Heat.